[video game music playing]
[video game zapping, beeping]
[video game zapping continues]
[entry bell jangles]
[man coughs]
[men rifling through food]
Hey, sir?
You need to pay first.
[grunts]
-[hip-hop beat playing]
-[cashier groaning]
[man 1] Yo.
Yo.
[shuddering]
Open it.
Open what?
[blade clicks]
[man 1] Open the fucking register.
[man 1] Yo.
Where's all the money?
Um… um…
-Answer him, you fucking punk-ass.
-[cashier whimpering]
-Everybody, uh… people, they…
-[man 1] Shit…
Nobody has cash. They pay with cards.
-[man 2] I'll take this.
-[man 1] Hey, hey. Yo.
-[cashier] Yes?
-That safe in the back…
-Uh… what?
-[man 1] The safe in the back.
-[cashier] Safe?
-The safe, back there.
-What's in the safe?
-Safe? What… I-I don't know.
I work part-time.
-I have no idea what's in there.
-[woman] Excuse me.
I wanna pay for this.
[man 1] Pay for it?
[money rustling]
-Is there any change?
-Ch-change?
I… I don't know. Uh…
Change… [chuckles nervously]
Uh…
There's not really enough in here…
[tense music playing]
I'll grab it from here. Yeah?
[man 1] Yo.
You stupid?
-[knife clatters]
-[man 1 screams]
Shit.
-[crunching]
-[cries out]
-Shit.
-Fuck.
[man 3 grunting] Oh shit!
You bitch!
[man 4] Hey!
[stabs]
[can clatters]
[shudders, sniffs]
I'd like to, uh, pay for this one as well.
Yeah?
[sniffs]
[arpeggiated electronic music playing]
[ethereal pop music playing]
[bone snaps]
[phone vibrating]
Hello?
[woman] Hello?
Hello? Ok-ju?
Yeah, hello? [clears throat]
Were you asleep?
No, uh, I was awake.
I haven't called in a while.
-Yeah, I know.
-Yeah.
It's been a while, huh?
Sorry.
There's been a lot going on.
My performing schedule's been crazy too…
till yesterday
I… You were performing yesterday.
Ok-ju…
are you… do you have time right now?
Yeah, um…
I'm, uh… I'm free right now.
[engine starts, revs]
[tires screech]
[mysterious music playing]
-[engine stops]
-[music stops]
[pop music playing faintly over speakers]
You've been busy. It's been a while.
[sighs] Yeah, you're right.
I'm, um… I'm sorry about that.
How've you been?
One day at a time, keeping a low profile…
Are you back to work?
I'm not… busy with work.
I've just been busy with other things.
You've lost some weight, haven't you?
-Are you on a diet?
-Right, like I would.
Four straws, right?
Blue, pink, yellow, green…
You remembered.
Free gift.
It's Turkish sausage. It's good.
Salty, but good.
[chuckles]
Come see me again!
[distant siren wailing]
Min-hee.
Min-hee, I'm letting myself in!
[whirs]
[melody plays]
[gentle music playing]
[man moaning in distance]
[gentle music playing loudly]
[music stops]
PLEASE GET REVENGE FOR ME!
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE ABLE TO HELP
[line ringing]
[ringtone playing in distance]
[ringtone playing loudly]
[ringtone continues]
[ominous music playing]
[ominous music intensifies]
[music stops]
[melancholy music playing]
[woman] Oh!
Sorry, we're closed.
Uh, you're closed?
I'll come back some other time, then.
No, come back!
I can maybe close later.
Uh, if there's something you wanna order.
[gentle pop music echoing from earbuds]
[music builds]
I'll take this one here.
-The mint chocolate?
-Yes.
Wait just one moment.
Is it someone's birthday?
Yeah.
Whose is it?
I wrap the cakes differently depending on
who's gonna be receiving the cake.
Um… there's no need to wrap it.
It should be pretty.
Our shop is famous
for beautiful packaging.
Your boyfriend's birthday?
Uh, no.
Then, um… family?
-Is it a friend?
-[scissors snipping]
It's my birthday.
Huh? No way!
-It's your birthday today?
-Huh?
Jang Ok-ju, don't you remember me?
From Yehwa School.
Choi Min-hee from the eighth grade!
[chuckles] Wow. So surreal.
We ran into each other on your birthday.
I know, right?
So, how are you? How's life?
-Mine?
-Yours! Duh!
[giggles]
Mmm… I mean, you know,
I do… all sorts of stuff.
But what do you do?
Uh… I work for a company overseas.
When domestic businesses, um,
travel to places like the Middle East
or Africa, anywhere abroad,
basically I work security, and escort.
Protect all the VIPs. Stuff like that.
Whoa, that's so cool.
Oh my God,
are you a bodyguard killer or what?
Nothing like that. I wish it were so cool.
[Min-hee chuckles]
-And you?
-Me?
I do ballet.
[echoing] Ballerina.
PLEASE AVENGE ME!
[suspenseful music playing]
[whirs]
[engine starts]
[tires screech]
[keys tapping]
[mouse clicking]
SEASONAL OMAKASE BENTO BOX
ORDER THROUGH CHITCHAT DM
TO-GO ORDERS ONLY
SUSHI OF THE DAY!
ENJOY OMAKASE AT HOME
DM FOR ORDERS
[keys tapping]
HELLO, MAY I PLACE AN ORDER?
[dings]
I'M CURRENTLY SELLING SUSHI
PAYMENTS IN BITCOIN ONLY
CAN I ORDER A BOX?
HOW MANY SOY SAUCE PACKETS?
I JUST NEED
ONE SOY SAUCE PACKET PLEASE
CHEF.CHOI HAS LEFT THE CHAT
[tranquil music playing]
Just this once.
[sighs] Do I have to? I wanna go--
Come on, don't make me beg you again.
Oh.
[tranquil music continues]
One…
Stop pouting. Cheese!
-One, two, three.
-[clicking]
[laughs]
-[clicks]
-[laughs]
[tranquil music continues]
[no audible dialogue]
[Ok-ju] I thought
that one day,
I could get shot and die
while doing this job and just not care.
I was like a zombie.
Or, you know, like I was numb.
[sighs]
But since that day I ran into you,
I realized that life
could actually be fun.
You helped me to come alive.
For the first time, I wasn't suffocating.
[Min-hee sighs] You're crazy.
[Ok-ju] Hmm?
What do you mean, "you could die"?
[phone ringing]
[phone continues ringing]
[man] Hello?
Hello?
Not fucking answering me again?
You have time for friends, but not for me?
If your friends knew who you really were,
would they still hang out with you?
[man sighs heavily]
Little bitch.
Meet at Jamsu Bridge tomorrow.
We open shop at 2:00 a.m.
If you ditch me again,
I'll make your friends hate you
and all your family disown you.
Choose wisely.
[line disconnects]
[tense music playing]
[tense music continues]
[phone vibrating]
[line ringing]
[phone continues vibrating]
-[line rings]
-[woman] Your call could not be connected.
-[man scoffs]
-[woman] Please leave a message--
[motorcycle revving]
[ominous electronic music playing]
[smooth hip-hop music playing]
[music fades]
[ethereal music playing]
[panting slowly]
[ethereal music continues]
[engine revving]
[gate clicks]
[upbeat music playing in car]
[groans]
Oh, that fucking bastard's blowing
through here with that fucking car.
Ah, Christ.
He done made a whole mess
of these chili peppers. A whole mess!
[suspenseful music playing]
[lock clicks]
[whimsical music playing]
[whimsical music continues]
[sighs]
[sinister music blares]
[unsettling music playing]
HALF JAPANESE
HIGH SCHOOLER
PIANIST
FIT MODEL
[unsettling music continues]
BALLERINA
[pensive music playing]
[jangling on video]
[heavy breathing]
[heavy breathing echoes]
[somber piano and string music playing]
-[gasping]
-[bone snaps]
[high-pitched ringing]
[echoing laughter]
[panting]
[audience murmuring]
[audience chatter intensifies]
[no audible dialogue]
[tense music playing]
[gentle piano music playing]
[sobbing]
[screams]
[gentle music builds]
[music stops]
HAND CAR WASH
[mysterious music playing]
[lighter clicks]
[mysterious music builds]
[mysterious music echoing from headphones]
[music stops]
[man] Hello?
Tomorrow?
I don't know.
Not in the mood.
Yeah. Let's go fishing.
Tomorrow's Friday anyway.
[sighs] No, not Aria.
Let's meet at Heaven.
[laughs] The girls at Aria are too easy.
Yeah, I guess. Easy girls are boring.
A challenge is more fun.
Anyway, I'll see you tomorrow. Later.
[mysterious music resumes]
FISHING, ARIA, HEAVEN
[light switch clicks]
[suspenseful music playing]
[hip-hop music playing]
♪ This is how I do it ♪
♪ This is how I do it
I… I… I do it ♪
♪ This is how I do it ♪
♪ This is how I do it
I… I… I do it ♪
This is how I do it ♪
♪ This is how I do it ♪
♪ This is how I do it
This is how I do it ♪
♪ This is how I do it ♪
♪ This is how I do it
This is how I… ♪
This is who… ♪
Here's your milkshake.
Thanks so much.
[bartender] Enjoy.
[hip-hop music continues]
♪ This is how I do it ♪
This is how I do it… ♪
[music fades]
-[man] Excuse me.
-[Ok-ju gasps]
Wow. Long time no see.
I can't believe I ran into you here.
[chuckles]
So, how've you been?
Who are you?
Wait, what do you mean?
You're Bo-ram? Park Bo-ram?
I'm not Park Bo-ram.
Oh. I'm really sorry about that.
You look so much like someone I know.
I thought you were her.
It's all right.
It happens.
Apologies.
[Ok-ju] Hey, wait.
Can I, like, buy you a drink?
[hip-hop music playing]
[engine roars]
So, uh, where are we going?
I mean, are we going to your house?
Mine? [scoffs]
What? You wanna meet my parents?
I just met you.
[both chuckle]
My parents are living with me.
I know a hotel.
It's a pretty cool place… in Gapyeong.
Not many people know about it.
They're like…
kind of like a private club.
What's so special about this hotel?
Just you wait.
I think you're gonna love it.
[hip-hop music continues]
[engine roars]
[relaxing music playing]
[rings bell twice]
[man] One moment, please.
Checking in?
Yes.
-Your suite at the end of the hall, yeah?
-Sure thing.
[clerk] Oh, can I get your car keys?
-[man] Ah.
-[keys jangle]
[elevator dings]
Your left.
[man] Mm.
Unique vibe, right?
It's like a royal Chinese palace.
[chuckles]
It looks cheap on the outside…
but cool on the inside.
Huh?
Normally, you can see
the woods out this window.
And in the morning,
the view from this room is incredible.
Yeah. That doesn't matter
when it's pitch dark.
[wind howling]
[laughs] Why is this so awkward?
You want a drink?
[ominous music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[panting slowly]
-[sharp jab]
-[whirring]
[menacing music playing]
[Ok-ju shuddering]
Shit!
Shit.
You fucking little bitch!
[menacing music continues]
[screams]
[Ok-ju] Fucker!
[man] Fuck you!
[man wailing]
[Ok-ju mutters]
[wailing]
[man coughing]
[man screaming]
[door opens]
[clerk] Fucking shit!
[gun clicking]
Aw, shit.
[smooth hip-hop music playing]
[Ok-ju panting]
Ah, shit.
[chain saw buzzing]
[revving chain saw]
-[man shrieks]
-[squelching]
[man] What the… what the fuck!
[continues shrieking]
[intense choral music playing]
[gunshot]
[man shrieking] I'm okay! I'm okay…
[engine revving]
[music fades]
[exhales]
[man] Sir.
You know, I must say,
you look more like a man now.
You were too pretty.
[lighter clicking]
[man chuckles] Weren't you
the best fighter among us?
-I guess those days are behind you.
-[muttering]
[coughing]
You bought a Lamborghini.
How much do those cost?
Three hundred million?
I don't know much about cars.
Where'd you get the money?
[coughing] From, uh,
part-time jobs.
[scoffs] "Part-time."
Oh, you work part-time?
Yes.
I know we, um,
push some dope, traffic women,
kill a few people.
But there are still
some traditions we have to uphold here.
Kim Du-han, Al Capone,
we all follow the same creeds, you know?
[sighs]
I told you to manage the girls,
but I didn't tell you to sell your fishies
and use the girls to make weird porn.
[sighs]
Hey, friend.
-Sir.
-God damn it.
Friend.
Come on. Here.
[sighs] Nice example, hmm?
Look at all of our young recruits.
You let them all down.
They're fucking cramped
in this tiny room because of you.
I'm sorry.
I'll take care of everything.
[sighs] By when?
As soon as possible.
That's your fucking answer?
Hey, friend.
You think I'm here to check up on you?
No.
[groaning]
[gasping]
[sighs]
You have three days
to bring that girl to me.
Understood?
[panting]
Burger?
Keeping your mouth shut?
[sighs]
-Excuse me?
-[server] Yes?
Two original burger meals, please.
-[server] Coming right up.
-Thank you.
[girl] Excuse me.
[server] Yes?
Could I get the ketchup on the side
and make mine with no onions?
I'd also like a cherry soda instead.
Sure. I'll get that started for you.
[Ok-ju sighs] How long
have you been there?
You know they call us slaves?
Slaves?
"It'll be over after this."
"Refuse?"
"I could leak the video
to all your classmates."
"Wanna be recognized by the whole nation?"
[gasps]
They're probably grooming
so many more girls too.
If we don't do what they say,
they'll upload it all.
Upload what exactly?
What do you think exactly? The videos.
[sighs]
[girl] It's okay now.
[giggles]
You're the one who's gonna save us all.
I prayed, you know.
I prayed for someone to show up.
My plan can work now 'cause you're here
You have a plan?
They're all gonna die.
I must have killed them
hundreds of times in my mind.
[suspenseful music playing]
[music stops]
PHARMACY
Hello.
Open the door.
Come on.
Well, look who came to visit me.
The news surprised the hell out of me
when I heard about it.
How could something so egregious happen
to the great and professional Mr. Choi?
Huh? Wow. Wow, your face is
pretty fucked up. [laughing]
It's insane.
[whirring]
[air hissing]
[man] So… what should we do?
Seriously, that stupid bitch
really left you totally crippled.
You were born
too handsome of a guy anyway, you know.
You also have better fashion sense
than most people.
This makes you… much more of a badass.
Was it one of our goddamn slaves?
[sighs]
No. I would have known her.
I've never seen her before.
Then maybe you should hire
one of the Yanbian and put out a hit.
For one girl?
That's a bit much.
[lighter clicking]
[exhales]
I mean, it's something
you and I can handle.
Why do you always have to make things
harder than they should be, huh?
Myung-shik.
She took my face.
She took my Lamborghini.
My face and my Lamborghini.
[unsettling music playing]
I know.
Yeah, man, I don't know. [scoffs]
It's not like I'm a hit man or anything.
You know that I'm a pharmacist.
It's not my job.
I mean, it's not like
it's in my blood to be a brutal murderer.
I'll give you a hundred million.
A hundred million won?
It won't take long.
Two days, max.
Yeah, but you're not talking about BDSM.
You're talkin' killing a real girl.
Yeah.
[Myung-shik] Are we filming it?
Why would we film it?
Some people film it overseas.
The films are called the snuff genre.
[sighs]
Myung-shik.
[eerie tones echoing]
Do I look like I'm joking?
No.
[gunfire]
A little lower.
Gun down.
[cocks gun]
What happened to your face?
You've been wandering long enough.
Come back.
It's impossible to find your replacement.
That's not why I'm here.
I'm not here to get my job back.
I… need some equipment.
Something untraceable.
You remember my friend… Min-hee,
I told you.
Ballerina.
Well, she… she died.
She ended her life a few days ago.
It's a bit complicated.
So now… I have to help her out.
Ok-ju, I…
I don't know
what it is that you need to do,
but is this really the only way?
You could report it to the police
and maybe they could help--
[Ok-ju] I have to do it.
I owe her that.
Will you help me, Mun-yeong?
Help me get a gun?
[tense music playing]
[vehicle approaching]
[music stops]
You?
What?
Are you the one
who wanted to buy from us, hmm?
Um,
yeah.
Hmm. So…
Uh, just one minute.
[man] Whoa. Take a look at that fancy car.
That thing is… it's just…
-So fire.
-Yeah.
Por… porchay… por…
Is that a new release or…
[blows]
Follow me.
[whimsical music playing]
So, um, fire, huh?
Hold it. Come on, don't be shy.
You better feel it for yourself. Hmm?
-A bit heavy?
-[sighs]
Is this all you have?
This one won't even load.
Every gun can be loaded, seriously.
You're just bad at it, for heaven's sake.
-Oil dried up or what? What the heck?
-[gun clicking]
Stupid piece of…
This one's busted.
-Gosh dang it. [sucks teeth]
-[guns clatter]
Just pick another one.
[riffling through guns]
Hey, mister.
Do you have anything decent?
Who uses revolvers anymore?
Well, they've all been saying
retro's coming back or something…
[Ok-ju] What's this?
Is this a toy gun?
What do you mean by "toy gun"?
Where's your appreciation for classics?
This gun will be your best bud
when you're caught in a pickle.
See it?
I bet you can't.
Someone puts a gun to your head.
"Ah shit." They ask,
"What's your last wish?"
"One last smoke?" "Smoke away."
You reach for a cigarette and…
Bang! Bang!
Sean Connery. You know that guy?
He carries this a lot.
This is not just a simple toy.
Just leave it here.
[woman] Hey!
What are you using it for?
Tell us about that.
-[Ok-ju] What's it for?
-Mm-hmm.
I guess…
I guess I'll be hunting.
[woman] Hunting?
[man] Uh-oh.
[woman sighs] This baby right… here.
Its purpose is
destroying wasp nests. Here.
Watch this. Shoo, shoo! Move away.
[clicks]
Ah yeah.
Pretty sick, huh?
[man] Sir, yes, sir! I love you, sir!
Have you been well?
I've been doing well.
I mean, I can't complain.
Hey, listen, Detective Kim,
you've been a big help
in bringing me money.
Ah. I'm calling
because I need help finding a car.
Not a burner car.
It's 19U 9322.
A Lamborghini.
Can you say that back to me?
All right. By the way, why don't you, uh,
stop by our pharmacy?
We've been stocking up on what you like.
[laughing]
Oh, you and your humor, Detective, huh?
Ah. You are too much for me,
Detective Kim! Huh?
[laughs]
I'll be waiting for your call.
[sighs]
Why's he wasting time
washing the car right now, huh?
He's probably a sociopath.
Seriously. Shit.
-[knocking at window]
-Huh?
W-what?
-What is it?
-Come over here.
Look down there.
What the hell?
[ominous music playing]
What the… what is that?
What is that?
Is it a location thingy? Fucking hell.
[music fades]
[clicking]
[girl] When are you gonna do it?
They could get the jump on us
if we take our time.
We have to be smart.
We tried once, so they'll be
ready and waiting for us now.
Whatever.
You better not mess this up for us.
[sighs]
Teach me to shoot a gun so I can help you.
[inhales deeply]
Go to sleep. Stop being a brat.
[girl] We need to finish this soon.
[beeps]
[TV playing]
[exhales]
[Ok-ju] One second.
[Min-hee] ♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Clap, clap.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ We all love you, dear Ok-ju ♪
♪ Happy birthday, happy day ♪
Ooh!  [claps]
Oh! By the way, team mint choc? [chuckles]
What's a mint choc?
You don't know that?
Mint choc-olate. [laughs]
Ah. Of course.
[both laugh]
I just… haven't tried it before.
Then why'd you pick this one?
Well, you said
you were closing up the shop
so I figured I'd pick the most simple one
you had there, you know.
Come on, why would you do that?
But that's so disrespectful
to all those beautiful cakes.
Ah…
Also, but this one looked like
the most beautiful one there too.
Mmm.
[laughing]
-[beeping]
-[Ok-ju] Hey!
Are you team mint choc?
Hey.
Where'd she go?
[rustling]
Hey!
[man shouting]
-[man] Fuck her!
-[blows landing]
[both grunting]
[Ok-ju screams]
[horse whinnying]
[man] Are you sure no one saw you?
[Choi] No one.
What did you do with the body?
Chopped it up and buried it
in the mountain, sir.
Which mountain?
[Choi] Bugaksan was behind her house.
Ah.
[man sighs]
I don't recall telling you to kill her.
I told you to bring her to me.
Wrap up your business
and hand everything over to Alien.
What do you mean--
I heard your fishies are
making you some good money.
High demand.
Stop operating independently.
Our ring can help you with distribution.
[Velcro ripping]
You're not answering me.
I don't need the ring's help.
I've been running it on my own.
If you give me your permission,
I can take care of it.
All right, get lost.
Who is that?
What a mess. An absolute mess, eh?
Is this an orphanage?
It's not. Leave her up to me, sir.
And what exactly will you do with her?
-She's young. We don't have to--
-You said she saw you murder that girl.
Doesn't that make her a witness?
It does.
"It does"?
I'll make sure that she doesn't speak.
[laughing] Oh man.
It's hard to believe
a little pussy like you
walks around
with a dick in his pants. Hmm?
Seriously.
I don't know anymore.
You're an enigma, friend.
[ominous music playing]
[horses whinnying]
[man] You like that?
Feels good, huh?
It's a shame
the water pressure's a little bit weak.
Wanna shower together, hmm?
It's so refreshing. I'm kind of sweaty.
Doesn't that feel so good?
Oh, I bet it feels so good.
Just so you know, I'm disappointed.
I was always kind to you.
I treated you special,
unlike the other girls
I thought we really had something,
I don't know, precious, me and you.
Do you remember what I told you?
I told you to stick it out a bit longer
and it'd be over soon.
Then you fucked it up.
Huh?
[Choi sighs]
Did being a sidekick for that bitch
make you feel badass?
Did it make you feel like you mattered?
Oh yeah?
You're looking at me?
Lower your head.
You little brat, how dare you?
The adults are talking right now.
My god. That sneaky bitch
really messed with this girl's head.
It's better for you if you open your mouth
and tell us where she is,
you stupid little fucking brat.
[groans]
Turn around
and put your hands on the wall.
We're going to start all over again
with you today, understand?
[suspenseful music playing]
[whip cracking]
[clerk] Of course, sir.
All our girls are young.
No.
We only have young girls, sir. Yeah.
Ah, I see.
Yeah, but you don't have to worry.
We have an agreement
with the local police officials, so…
-Yeah, yeah.
-[bell rings]
[man groans]
Of course, sir.
We're members only.
We're not like a brothel in Seoul, sir.
-Right.
-[bell rings]
[man gasps]
Our hours?
Feel free to drop by
anytime you want. Weekdays, weekend.
I got a customer. Bye.
[door closes]
[thud]
[groans]
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
[gun clicks]
This bitch.
[music fades]
I'm only going to ask this once.
Where is that bastard?
[tense music continues]
[silence]
This pair was so hard to find,
you know that?
[gun clicking]
[Min-hee]
I'm going to study ballet properly.
Russia has the finest schools.
I won't be here for your birthday,
so here's your present.
[ominous music playing]
[singers vocalizing]
[horses nickering, whinnying]
[suspenseful music playing]
Let me ask you something.
Has anybody seen a girl
who's about this tall?
[snickers]
If you tell me where she is
without running your mouths
and asking me any questions…
[man 1] Oh shit.
[men murmuring]
…I'll leave this place alone.
Which one of you dumb bastards
can tell me where she is?
[man 2] So you're the girl.
And he told me he buried you
in Bugaksan, damn it.
Choi, that fucking piece of shit.
[chuckles]
Looks like you've been through hell.
Come here and sit.
I'm glad you came. So, let's talk.
I mean, there's no reason
for you to fight with us, is there?
I don't have
a personal grudge against you--
-[silenced gunshot]
-[men gasp]
-I'll ask one more time.
-[men murmuring]
Can anybody here tell me?
[man 3] No! Come on!
[men whimper]
That's too bad.
[clicks]
[gun clicks empty]
You piece of shit bitch!
[tense music playing]
-[man 4] Get her!
-[men shouting ferociously]
[hip-hop music playing]
Get back!
[man 5] Come on, bitch!
Bitch! Bitch!
[music fades]
[Ok-ju panting]
Ready to tell me what I wanna hear?
[man shudders]
Where is that asshole?
Fuck yourself, bitch.
Okay.
All right.
You made me.
[man screaming]
[Ok-ju shrieks]
[menacing music playing]
[kicks table]
[horse nickers]
[whinnying]
[laughs softly]
[gunshot]
[Ok-ju groaning]
[gasping]
Ah shit, fuck. Fuck.
What a satanic bitch, wow.
Wow, talk about fucking perfect timing.
Good job, man.
That fucking gun. Where did you get that?
[exhales] Good job. You're good.
I'll clean it up. A hundred million.
Send the money. Huh?
Where the fuck did she go?
Oh fuck.
You think you're the only one with a gun?
You're not the only one
with a big-ass gun!
Hundred million, my ass.
Piece of shit. Everybody's dead.
[tense music playing]
[gunshot]
[gun clicks empty]
[horse neighing]
-[gunshot]
-[girl gasps]
[Choi groaning]
[Choi gasping]
[groaning]
[girl moaning]
[gentle music playing]
[straining]
[Choi groans]
[Choi moaning]
[whimpering] Oh shit, oh shit!
Fucking bitch!
[screams]
Fucking shit!
[whimpering, gasping]
You've blown things way out of proportion.
You know?
Hey, there's… there's no reason to…
take things this far.
You're fucking overreacting.
[Ok-ju] Figures.
You probably never imagined
how capable we'd be at fucking you up.
You assumed we were prey.
You're a crazy bitch.
I don't even know who you are!
I mean, why the hell
are you even going this far?!
-Shit!
-Don't you remember?
I've never even fucking met you! [screams]
Me?
I'm the ballerina.
[choral music playing]
-[gas hissing]
-Hey! Hey!
Hold… hold on, just hold on!
Stop! I'm sorry!
[moans] I'm really sorry.
I'll spend the rest of my life repenting!
Wait, I'll… I'll face legal punishment.
I'll give you all my money!
All of it, okay?!
I mean, honestly, shit! [sobbing]
I didn't do anything bad enough
to deserve to fucking die!
[Ok-ju] Shut up!
[retching, sobbing]
Hold on.
Let me ask you one thing.
Was that woman really a ballerina?
I thought that she was fucking lying.
I mean, what ballerina is fat?
I saw her naked and everything.
[laughing]
You're laughing?
[Choi laughing loudly]
If you kill me, you better watch out.
When I see that bitch in hell,
I'm gonna keep doing
the same things to her.
You want that?
Try me.
Because you'll be my prey in hell.
[clicking]
[Choi] No! No!
[screams] No!
[Choi screaming]
[choral music intensifies]
[Choi stops screaming]
[music stops]
[gasping]
[peaceful music playing]
[Min-hee laughing] Isn't it amazing?
Nobody else knows about it.
It's my secret spot.
Oh God, I used to take
the train here all the time.
Did you always like the sea?
Didn't I tell you?
I'm gonna come back
as a fish in my next life.
I'm only doing ballet right now
because I can't become a fish yet.
[Ok-ju] Of all things,
you wanna be reborn as a fish?
"Of all things"?
[scoffs] I believe
that the earth belongs to the fish.
And us humans
are just living in their world.
Wow! Look at that.
Ok-ju… look.
Don't you feel free?
[peaceful music continues]
[jangling]
MON 2:00 AM, COEX SQUARE
FRI 2:30 AM, JAMSU BRIDGE
FRI 2:30 AM, YONGSAN STATION
THU 1:30 AM, SEOUL PLAZA
FRI 2:30 AM, BONGEUNSA ENTRANCE
[pensive music playing]
[gentle pop ballad playing]
♪ Blood on my hands ♪